in today's world the internet is where
consumers discover local businesses like
yours so having a strong online presence
is
crucial but building one is time
consuming and complex and hiring someone
to do it for you is
expensive until now meet Madison your
new AI powerered digital marketing
specialist improving SEO managing social
media and uncovering actionable insights
for asow low as $99 a
month it's simple just connect your
business's
accounts and Madison helps you show up
higher on
Google by SEO optimizing your Google
business
profile crafting tailored review
responses across all
platforms simply review modify if needed
and approve over time Madison learns
your Brand's voice and by increasing
your ratings and reviews through
simplified review requests only
directing the positive ones to Google to
be posted
publicly Madison also expands your
social media reach by automatically
creating targeting and scheduling
engaging campaigns again simply review
modify if needed and approve and if you
want to announce a promotion or new
offering or just say hi simply tell
Madison Madison also uncovers actionable
insights by
centralizing and visualizing key
analytics it makes understanding what
your customers think as simple as
asking ready to acquire new customers
without the crazy cost go to meet
[Music]
madison.